The most difficult moment coincides
with the Brother Leman cascade in 2008 and
the orders begin to close and
run out.  We started to have a
significant fear, we made
significant staff reductions, my
brother was already taken over by the company, we
suspended our salaries for 2 years,
he and I, mom, so that was
also a moment in our family, in the company,
where we were defeated and in that moment
then how the slow factory was born in that
moment where we realized instead that in the
factory we knew how to do a mess of things
which is that attitude, let's say,
Italian, especially in this segment
where there are intelligent hands
[music] inside the factories who are
those things that invent the processes,
the ways to solve a
manufacturing problem.   Did
you end up getting Armani as a
client back then or did he just walk away?  It didn't
escape you, so you know it?  Yes, yes.